[{"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Billy Ray, how are you?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "If that were the case, that's what it's going to read.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "So my first question is, did you ever have this terrible nagging feeling that if you suddenly keeled over from a heart attack tomorrow, the headlines would be, Miley Cyrus' dad dies of an achey breaky heart?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "YRUS: I would sum it up as, for every action, there is an opposite and equal reaction.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "As you approach it, how would you sum up your life?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "I'd kind of like to know some vanilla.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "And as a musician all your life, does being able to have both extremes in your life, is that good for the creative process?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "And when you see Miley occasionally falling off the straight and narrow, do you recognize that slightly rebellious edge to her?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I've learned that it's not how many times you get knocked down, it's how many times you get back up.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What have you learned about yourself over the last 50 years?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Dust yourself off.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "And what's the key to getting back on your feet when you've had a big blow?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Well, the best -- the best being here with you.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What would you say have been the best and worst moments of your life?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "And what would you say had been the worst moment of your life?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What would you least want to go through?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, he had a real love of music.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What were his values that he tried to instill in you?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, I share that a lot with Miley, and with all my kids.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "If you ever think about it, ever wonder what he would have said?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, I do look extremely happy.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "When you watch yourself, though, what are you honestly thinking when you see yourself there?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "A year before that.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "A year before that?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "I was 29.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "So you would have been, what, about 29?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, the dream was and the prayer was that I would pray that God would give me the wisdom and the vision to sing the songs I was supposed to sing, to do the things I was supposed to do, to be the person I was supposed to be, and through my life and my music, I prayed that God would give me the ability to represent the light and his love.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And what's the dream when you're in that car?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, I had 10 songs recorded for the album.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized this song was going to change your life?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "The night that we did the video in Ashland, Kentucky, that very nice, I felt like something changed.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "When did you get a call or somebody said, you thought, wow, OK, this is going?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I got really busy, and started getting on a lot of airplanes and getting in a lot of limousines.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What happened when the teeter goes to totter?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I was.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Well, you were on your own, weren't you?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I was definitely dealing with a lot in my world.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "It's what you felt, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Shoot, I don't know, you know.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "How did Miley actually react to the interview?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "It was such a -- again, a dark time.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "The next time you spoke to her, what did she say?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "You kids are my dream.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How can I stop you from having yours?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I just knew that there was a whole lot of change ahead.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Knowing how many child stars in particular end up in a very dysfunctional way in their lives?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I couldn't really -- at that moment, you know, it's best to just -- you know if you hear the words of the song, you know, she's got to do what she's got to do.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Were you frightened?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Would you take that option?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "And underage drinking.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Was it about me?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "It's amazing.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Great clip, isn't it?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "You know, I think that might be one in itself, is that -- she really -- she's the real deal.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What are probably the biggest misconceptions about your daughter, do you think?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Didn't see anything horribly wrong about it.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "What is your -- looking back on it, a storm in a teacup?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Were you surprised that people said they were inappropriate?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Bong gate happened in the midst of my darkness -- in my darkest hour.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Was the -- was the bong gate scandal worse for you to deal with?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "By then, I -- I was probably -- I was a bit numb of pain at that time.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "So you took it worse perhaps than you would have done?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Do you think she realized that?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Oh, heck yes.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Not professionally, but are you proud of her for the way that she has dealt with these mini scandals?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Really good.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "And how is your relationship with her now, would you say?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I look back on it.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "But since she's been famous, do you think you now have a stronger relationship than you've had before?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, I think when you look back on it, and you go, \"What went wrong?\"", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "And then what went right, when you look back?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "You know, I just prayed for vision and strength, and wisdom to communicate.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "How did you -- how did you win your wife back?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Given that the -- the -- this ride that you talk about, this rocket ride was part of the problem.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "I think it was more about step by step, you know?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Communication is the key.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "How have you adjusted things now so that it works better for all of you?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Everybody just talk at what's on your mind.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "So talking?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "I -- I'm guessing so.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "When you got back?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Yes, and I think probably -- did your mind flash back to how you felt as a five year old?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "What does it stand for?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "It's the land of the free, the home of the brave.", "docId": "110712pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "What does being an American mean to you?", "qSentId": 663}]